http://www.iacr.org/privacy.html

IACR Privacy Policy
The following statement discloses the IACR's information gathering and
dissemination practices.
The IACR maintains a website and other online services for the purpose of running its operations and achieving its goals. The IACR is committed to not collect or store personal data and other sensitive information beyond the extent needed to satisfy its mission.
The IACR maintains member databases that contain mailing, billing, and member profile information, as well as a record of each member's registrations for conferences. The information in these databases is used by authorized officers and Board-delegated organization staff to process registrations; mail invoices, renewal notices, and announcements; and respond to member inquiries. Members can update their contact information using the online from found at
https://secure.iacr.org/membership/
. This information is automatically updated whenever a new conference registration is submitted or upon renewal of a membership. Personal information is stored in a database and standard security methods are used to protect it. The IACR requires confirmation of identity before releasing information back to the user for update over the web.
The IACR records the IP address of computers interacting with its websites and services on its domains, such as *.iacr.org, ia.cr, and chesconference.org.
Credit card payments are handled by a third-party payment processor, which stores information according to its own privacy policy.
The IACR provides the third-party payment processor with mailing and billing information about the customer at the time of the transaction.
The IACR does not rent or sell email addresses, postal addresses, or other personal information.
The IACR may use email and postal addresses to conduct its operations, including contacting members regarding their membership status, conference registrations, and IACR elections, as well as sending occasional announcements about IACR events to those members who have not opted out of receiving such announcements.
The IACR may share this information with third parties who are carrying out these operations on its behalf.
The IACR provides a list of people registered for an IACR conference to attendees and members. Attendees to IACR conferences may choose to be omitted from the attendee list given to other attendees and members.
The IACR website and other communications of the IACR contain links to or resources from other sites. The IACR is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such websites.
